{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Practical Research 1",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Module 3 - Lesson 3",
    "LastModified": "14 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Module 3 - Lesson 3.pdf"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What is a question that a research project sets out to answer?",
      "answer": "Writing Research Questions",
      "choices": [
        "Writing Scope and Delimitation",
        "Writing Significance of the Study",
        "Writing Research Questions",
        "Writing a Research Title"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the initial step in a research project?",
      "answer": "Writing Research Questions",
      "choices": [
        "Writing a Research Title",
        "Writing Scope and Delimitation",
        "Writing Significance of the Study",
        "Writing Research Questions"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of a research question provides enough specifics that one's audience can easily understand its purpose without needing additional explanation?",
      "answer": "Clear",
      "choices": [
        "Focused",
        "Clear",
        "Concise",
        "Complex"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of a research question means it is narrow enough that it can be answered thoroughly?",
      "answer": "Focused",
      "choices": [
        "Arguable",
        "Complex",
        "Focused",
        "Clear"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of a research question means it is expressed in the fewest possible words?",
      "answer": "Concise",
      "choices": [
        "Concise",
        "Complex",
        "Arguable",
        "Focused"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of a research question is not answerable with a simple 'yes' or 'no', but requires synthesis and analysis of ideas?",
      "answer": "Complex",
      "choices": [
        "Clear",
        "Complex",
        "Concise",
        "Arguable"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What characteristic of a research question has potential answers that are open to debate rather than accepted facts?",
      "answer": "Arguable",
      "choices": [
        "Focused",
        "Clear",
        "Arguable",
        "Complex"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of research problem is the opening statement of your Statement of the Problem (S.O.P.)?",
      "answer": "General Problem",
      "choices": [
        "Specific Problem",
        "Scope",
        "Delimitation",
        "General Problem"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of research problem reflects the title of your research study?",
      "answer": "General Problem",
      "choices": [
        "General Problem",
        "Significance of the Study",
        "Specific Problem",
        "Scope"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of research problem are the questions that you want to be answered in your study?",
      "answer": "Specific Problem",
      "choices": [
        "General Problem",
        "Delimitation",
        "Specific Problem",
        "Scope"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the description of the scope of the study?",
      "answer": "Delimitation of study",
      "choices": [
        "Significance of the Study",
        "Delimitation of study",
        "General Problem",
        "Scope"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What will explain why definite aspects of a subject were chosen and why others were excluded?",
      "answer": "Delimitation of study",
      "choices": [
        "Specific Problem",
        "Scope",
        "Delimitation of study",
        "General Problem"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the parameters of your study?",
      "answer": "Scope",
      "choices": [
        "Delimitation",
        "Scope",
        "Significance of the Study",
        "General Problem"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the factors not included in your research study?",
      "answer": "Delimitation",
      "choices": [
        "Scope",
        "Specific Problem",
        "General Problem",
        "Delimitation"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What part of a research paper identifies the beneficiaries and the benefits that it will give when the problem is solved?",
      "answer": "Significance of the Study",
      "choices": [
        "Scope",
        "Delimitation",
        "Significance of the Study",
        "General Problem"
      ],
      "reference": "Designing Research Questions and Scope",
      "term": "Module 3 Lesson 3"
    }
  ]
}